{
    "id": "8d61700a2ad34643a0c20645be482c64",
    "title": "Determiners Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "There weren't ................................ students in the class.",
            "description": "We use many before plural nouns and much before uncountable nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "little",
                "much",
                "many"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "He doesn't have ................................. patience.",
            "description": "We use much before an uncountable noun.",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "many",
                "little",
                "a lot"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We haven't got ............................. time to prepare for the test.",
            "description": "We use much before uncountable nouns. ",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "many",
                "little"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I like your parents ............................",
            "description": "Much is not normally used with like and dislike in affirmative clauses.",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "a lot",
                "a lot of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I managed to solve the puzzle with .............................. difficulty.",
            "description": "We use little before uncountable nouns. ",
            "answers": [
                "little",
                "few",
                "many",
                "lesser"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I got ............................. apples than her.",
            "description": "Fewer is the comparative form of few. We use it before a plural noun.",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "fewer",
                "less",
                "lesser"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I earn ................................. than my sister.",
            "description": "In this context, less is the comparative form of little. ",
            "answers": [
                "fewer",
                "less",
                "lesser"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We experienced far .................................. problems than we were expecting.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "fewer",
                "less"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The company does not make ............................... money these days.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "much",
                "a lot"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "............................. want a new system.",
            "description": "Many is not normally used alone to mean 'many people'.",
            "answers": [
                "Many",
                "Many people",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She is extremely close to ................................. friends she has.",
            "description": "The few means not many but all that you have. ",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "a few",
                "the few"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I .............................. enjoyed my stay with your family.",
            "description": "Much can be an adverb.",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "a lot",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}